Hello everyone, I am Xueli.
Now personal users can also sell their digital products on Marvelous Designer's official website.
First of all, if you do not have a Marvelous Designer official website account, please click here to register.
After registration, please log in to your account.
After logging in, you will see a pop-up window on the shop menu.
This pop-up window will remind you that you are now open for business.
If you want to upload your own files, you need to click on the link below.
After clicking, it will jump to our Connect website.
After jumping to this page, we can upload our own files and sell them.
Connect website is for another software company under our company.
It is a website developed by Clou.
Clou users and MD users can sell their own 3D assets.
These 3D assets include, but not limited to, clothing, virtual models, and some accessories, such as buttons or fabrics, etc.
After logging in, click on this arrow in the upper right corner.
We can come to the file upload interface.
After opening the upload page,
we need to select the type of file we want to upload.
There are two types.
The left one is Closet Connect.
The uploaded files cannot be uploaded to the Marvelous Designer store at the same time.
If we select the option on the right,
the uploaded files will be uploaded to both Connect and MDStore at the same time.
So if you are a Marvelous Designer user,
please select the option on the right.
Remember to make sure that your account has been registered on the Marvelous Designer website.
Then click on the File button.
After that, find your 3D file in the browser window.
And select Confirm.
At the bottom, you can see the types of files we support uploading.
These include but not limited to, clothing, project files, virtual models, buttons, buttons, pull links, accessories, fabrics, etc.
At the bottom,
you can see the largest file size is 500MB.
When uploading files,
be careful not to exceed this size.
In addition, at the bottom,
you can see our service terms.
Click on it,
and you can see our service terms page.
After we upload the file,
you will see a prompt here.
Complete uploading,
then click on the next step.
Then it will jump to our details page.
First of all, if you want to replace the file,
you can click on Replace here.
Then at the bottom,
you can enter the title and name of this product.
you can enter the description of this product.
You can fill it in according to your needs.
Description can be your inspiration,
design idea, clothing structure, etc.
At the bottom,
you can add any labels you need to add.
After entering the label,
click on the Enter button to confirm.
You can add multiple labels at the same time.
If there are other attached,
you can choose to add here.
Also, pay attention here.
The whole product,
including the product itself and the component,
do not exceed 500MB.
Then at the bottom,
you can add some rendering images,
or any pictures you want to describe some details.
On the entire web page,
there is a filter in the right-hand position.
Here we can upload the cover image of the product.
There is only one cover image.
When our mouse clicks on the filter,
we can click on Replace to replace the cover image.
For the added image,
there is a trash can icon in the upper right corner of the image.
Click on this icon to delete the added image.
The added image can be added multiple times at the same time.
Then click Next to upload.
Before uploading,
we will classify the categories according to the file you uploaded.
If you upload a garment,
that is, a clothing file,
you need to select its gender,
clothing type,
and purpose of wearing.
Here I will choose to be a girl's dress.
On the right side,
we will see the type you have selected.
If you want to change it,
you can switch to other options
and click on the hook.
Most options can be selected multiple times.
Regarding the purpose of wearing,
it is the length of the clothes
applied to this set of clothes,
for example,
it may be military clothing,
daily clothing,
or clothing, etc.
For those who do not see clearly,
you can pause to see the translation.
After we have selected,
you can select the item you belong to at the bottom.
The creation of this album is decided by you.
After that,
we will show you how to create different albums.
After selecting the album,
at the bottom,
you can select the type of price and license.
Here you can choose to set the project as a paid project
or a free project.
If you set it as a paid project,
there are two types of fees below.
Among them,
the basic license price is for the purchase of goods
purchased by the user.
The price paid by the user below
is the fee paid for the purchase of goods
purchased by the enterprise user.
You can modify the price of this license
according to the need.
After the enterprise user buys the license,
they can use this file
they purchased in their various projects.
In addition,
you can set it as a free file
or a file that can only be checked.
Whether it is a free project
or a paid project,
there is a option called food production below.
When you select this option,
other users who have purchased this project
can produce food according to this project.
So everyone carefully select this option
and then we can click on the next step.
Here,
everyone should pay attention that
the settings of the paid project and the free project
are irreversible.
That is to say,
once you have selected one of them,
for example,
you have selected this project as a free project,
then after the next upload,
you can no longer switch to the paid project.
After the official upload,
we can see this project
that we uploaded
in the 3D viewfinder on the screen.
At the bottom of the screen,
you can select to delete this already uploaded project
or to edit and adjust
the information that was filled out
by it before.
The right side is the official release.
Next,
let's learn how to use this 3D viewfinder.
First of all,
as in our software,
when you slide the scroll wheel,
you can zoom in and out.
Press the right mouse button
and drag the mouse,
you can rotate it.
Press the middle mouse button
and drag it,
you can parallel.
Here,
we can choose to switch the display type.
If you switch to grid,
you can see the entire text.
You can see the grid distribution in the entire file.
If you choose single color,
you can see the white film effect.
The color next to it
is the function dedicated to cloud.
We don't need to do more research.
Next to it,
you can switch to display the background,
name or quantity,
and whether the virtual model is displayed.
Here,
I hope you can pay attention to this.
If the file you are selling
will be sold at the same time
on the MDStore,
please try to avoid
bringing the virtual model
with you.
And this set of clothing
you are selling
needs to be worn
on a virtual model
with the information of the wearer
in advance
and then stored.
This way,
you can wear the information of the wearer.
In addition,
the clothing you are selling
needs to be worn
in the form of the virtual model T-pose
and stored.
In fact,
these regulations about wearing clothes
are because
users who use Marvelous Designer
are mostly using
their own virtual models.
In order to quickly adapt
virtual models and these clothes,
we have these regulations.
If you need to adjust,
you can replace the file again.
Click the edit at the bottom
to go back to the edit page.
After going back to the edit page,
we can replace the file.
After clicking the replace,
we need to find the file
after replacement on our computer.
After replacing the file,
we need to enter the reason
for changing the file.
After replacing the file,
you may need to adjust
other descriptions and titles
and so on.
After adjusting,
click the next step again
to go back to the product classification page.
You can modify these types
according to your needs.
The system will automatically classify
the format of the file
you uploaded.
In other words,
if you uploaded fabric
or virtual models,
there will be corresponding settings
at the bottom.
Then we click the next step.
Click the image in the upper right corner of the web page
to come to my main page.
At the top of the web page,
you can click to upload a background picture.
The best size of this background picture
is 3280 pixels.
Here you can upload your own image
and enter your name,
choose your profession.
In the salad menu,
you can choose up to three professions,
and enter your contact information,
your location,
your main page link
and your self-introduction.
On the right side,
you can see the album you created.
At the bottom of the album name,
you can see all the projects
that belong to this album.
Click on the top of the list
to add a new album.
You can create a new album.
Here you can enter
the name of this album.
Click on the project,
you can change it to display all the projects.
Click on the upload on the right side of the screen
to upload the product.
On the right side of the upload,
you can see the share icon.
After clicking on the share icon,
you can directly copy
your main page link
and share it with others.
That's it for the tutorial on the store.
See you next time.
Bye bye.
Captions by GetTranscribed.com